<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>DNS - Tag - Robert Grzelka</title><link>https://robertgrzelka.pl/tags/dns/</link><description>DNS - Tag - Robert Grzelka</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>robert.grzelka@outlook.com (Robert Grzelka)</managingEditor><webMaster>robert.grzelka@outlook.com (Robert Grzelka)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 21:44:55 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robertgrzelka.pl/tags/dns/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Azure AKS use Cert Manager to generate TLS Cert with Azure DNS and Letsencrypt</title><link>https://robertgrzelka.pl/blog/azure/azure-aks-cert-manager-azure-dns-letsencrypt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 21:44:55 +0200</pubDate><author>Robert Grzelka</author><guid>https://robertgrzelka.pl/blog/azure/azure-aks-cert-manager-azure-dns-letsencrypt/</guid><description>Kubernetes Cert Manager with Azure DNS and LetsEncrypt Following my last piece on Azure DNS as external resource for SSL ACME Challenge, today, we are diving deep into securing Kubernetes clusters using the Cert-Manager to generate trusted TLS certificates, particularly for Nginx Ingress, with Azure DNS and Let’s Encrypt.
Introduction The quest for enhanced security in Kubernetes often leads to the integration of TLS certificates. Leveraging Cert Manager with Azure DNS and Let’s Encrypt simplifies this process, ensuring not only the automation of certificates issuance but also their renewal, enhancing the cluster’s security.</description></item><item><title>Azure AKS use Cert Manager to generate TLS Cert with Azure DNS and Letsencrypt</title><link>https://robertgrzelka.pl/blog/kubernetes/azure-aks-cert-manager-azure-dns-letsencrypt-copy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 21:44:55 +0200</pubDate><author>Robert Grzelka</author><guid>https://robertgrzelka.pl/blog/kubernetes/azure-aks-cert-manager-azure-dns-letsencrypt-copy/</guid><description>Kubernetes Cert Manager with Azure DNS and LetsEncrypt Following my last piece on Azure DNS as external resource for SSL ACME Challenge, today, we are diving deep into securing Kubernetes clusters using the Cert-Manager to generate trusted TLS certificates, particularly for Nginx Ingress, with Azure DNS and Let’s Encrypt.
Introduction The quest for enhanced security in Kubernetes often leads to the integration of TLS certificates. Leveraging Cert Manager with Azure DNS and Let’s Encrypt simplifies this process, ensuring not only the automation of certificates issuance but also their renewal, enhancing the cluster’s security.</description></item><item><title>Azure DNS as external resource for SSL ACME Challenge to bypass Ingress Firewalls</title><link>https://robertgrzelka.pl/blog/azure/azure-dns-for-letsencrypt-acme-challenge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 21:44:55 +0200</pubDate><author>Robert Grzelka</author><guid>https://robertgrzelka.pl/blog/azure/azure-dns-for-letsencrypt-acme-challenge/</guid><description>Securing Web Services with Azure DNS: Mastering the SSL ACME Challenge Secure web services are non-negotiable, and SSL/TLS certificates stand at the forefront of this security. While Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt offers these certificates, procuring them becomes a complex task if your server is shielded by a firewall that filters out incoming internet traffic. The culprit? Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt&amp;rsquo;s ACME challenge requests. Thankfully, Azure DNS comes to the rescue, providing a smooth path to your solution.</description></item><item><title>Azure Private Endpoints for VNET Integrated Ingress</title><link>https://robertgrzelka.pl/blog/azure/azure-private-endpoint/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 21:44:55 +0200</pubDate><author>Robert Grzelka</author><guid>https://robertgrzelka.pl/blog/azure/azure-private-endpoint/</guid><description>In my another article we described a Public Network Firewall Access Control. Today we will talk about Private Endpoints for VNET Integrated Ingress.
Networking is a crucial component of any cloud infrastructure. With Azure, you can design intricate network topologies that cater to various security, isolation, and connectivity needs. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to delve into Inbound Private Networking in Azure, focusing on Azure Private Endpoints and how they facilitate secure inbound connectivity.</description></item></channel></rss>