<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Robert Grzelka</title><link>https://robertgrzelka.pl/</link><description>Personal blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>robert.grzelka@outlook.com (Robert Grzelka)</managingEditor><webMaster>robert.grzelka@outlook.com (Robert Grzelka)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robertgrzelka.pl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Azure DevOps Pipeline Variable Types - Compile-time, Queue-time, and Run-time</title><link>https://robertgrzelka.pl/blog/azure/2023-10-01-azure-devops-variables/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 21:44:55 +0200</pubDate><author>Robert Grzelka</author><guid>https://robertgrzelka.pl/blog/azure/2023-10-01-azure-devops-variables/</guid><description>Azure DevOps: Understanding Compile-time, Queue-time, and Run-time Variables Azure DevOps stands as a formidable platform for continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD). Its power is enriched by its versatile variable management system. This article will guide you through the maze of Azure DevOps variables, revealing the hidden quirks and behaviors across different scopes.
Usecases This Post Will Answer: Ever been puzzled about how Azure DevOps Pipelines handle variables? Wondering how to leverage your pipeline with variable scopes?</description></item><item><title>Azure DNS as external resource for SSL ACME Challenge to bypass Ingress Firewalls</title><link>https://robertgrzelka.pl/blog/azure/2023-10-03-azure-dns-for-letsencrypt-acme-challenge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 21:44:55 +0200</pubDate><author>Robert Grzelka</author><guid>https://robertgrzelka.pl/blog/azure/2023-10-03-azure-dns-for-letsencrypt-acme-challenge/</guid><description>Securing Web Services with Azure DNS: Mastering the SSL ACME Challenge Secure web services are non-negotiable, and SSL/TLS certificates stand at the forefront of this security. While Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt offers these certificates, procuring them becomes a complex task if your server is shielded by a firewall that filters out incoming internet traffic. The culprit? Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt&amp;rsquo;s ACME challenge requests. Thankfully, Azure DNS comes to the rescue, providing a smooth path to your solution.</description></item><item><title>Basic Markdown Syntax</title><link>https://robertgrzelka.pl/blog/markdown/basics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 16:15:22 +0800</pubDate><author>Robert Grzelka</author><guid>https://robertgrzelka.pl/blog/markdown/basics/</guid><description>&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>